Wilson D'souza

Mobile - +918888065663

Email – wilsondsouza00785@gmail.com



Objective

To create a happy working environment for the team and help the team achieve excellence in Food and Beverage service and reach to its pinnacle by providing customer delight using my skills and capabilities.

A leader with above 7 years of experience in Hospitality with food and beverage service.

Self - motivated and result oriented.

An effective communicator with planning , coordination, people management and team building skills.

Guest and team focused.

Positive approach and possess eye for quality.

Work Experience

 Currently working as an Assistant restaurant manager with FOUR POINTS BY SHERATON PUNE from December 2016.

Accountable for daily restaurant operations.

Generating revenue reports.

Controlling of cost and planning to meet Budget.

Ensuring the team stays happy and focused at work.

Ensuring of daily briefings and trainings for the team members to meet the hotel standards.

Ensuring of daily system and cash closing procedures.

Maintaining of all the documents related to Audits.

Planning the stafffing and handling complaint resolving issues pertaining to guest and staff. Ensuring compliance with the restaurant SOP's.

- Worked as a Team Leader with Premier Inn, Kharadi, Pune.(Shift In charge) from May 20, 2013 to December 2,2014.
 - Taking care of the duty allocations, Handling guest complaints and doing the daily closing down procedures of the cash management system were the key terms of my job.
- Worked as a Supervisor in Hotel Rajtara, Satara, from December 1, 2010 to December 24, 2011.
- Worked as a Steward in the Gateway Hotel (TAJ group of Hotels), Vadodara for a period of 13 months from December 22, 2011 to January 10, 2013.
- Worked as a Purchase Operator in Minakshi Bazar from May 2004 to May 2005.
- Worked at the Counter Sale for Nokia Priority from June 2005 to May 2008.

Vocatioal Training

Hotel Maharaja Regency, Satara August 2008 – February 2009 (7 months)

Area of Specialization – Service

Industrial Training			
Department	Hotel	Duration	
F&B Service,			
F&B Production,	Eastern David Calarra Varia	May 21, 2009 to August	
Housekeeping and Front	Fortune Park Galaxy, Vapi	21, 2009 (3 months)	
Office			
F&B Production	Fortune Park Galaxy, Vapi	April 24, 2010 to July	
		22, 2010 (3 months)	

Education

Title	Board/University	Year of Passing	Class
B. Sc. In Hotel Management	Maharashtra Board	May 2014	1st class
Hotel Management & Catering Technology	Certificate course	April 2009	1 st class
XII	D. G. College, Shivaji University	February 2003	2 nd class
X	Nirmala Convent High School, Kolhapur Board	March 2001	1 st class

Extra Curricular & Achievements

- Awarded the best hospitality personality for the year 2017 on the occasion of International hospitality day held by IIHM.
- Have successfully cleared several Starwood audits and LRA(Lasner and rush associates)
- Have been awarded the Champ of the quarter, 2015 on the occasion of Customer service week.
- Have been recognized as Star performer, Front of the House on the occasion of Customer service week, 2015.
- Nominated for Champ of the year at Premier Inn across all hotels (Asia pacific)
- Participated in various activities such as Chess Tournament, Darts Tournament and
 Cricket tournament at the Gateway Hotel, Vadodara and emerged as the winner and runner
 up in cricket and chess.

Hobbies & Interests

- Swimming
- Listening to music

Strengths

- Passionate towards work
- Striving to achieve the best and getting out the best from the team.
- Pleasant personality
- Confident

Personal Details

Name: Wilson D'souza

Father's Name: Albert D'souza

Date of Birth: July 27, 1985

Age: 33 years

Marital Status: Married

Religion: Christian

Nationality: Indian

Languages known: English, Hindi, Marathi, Konkani

I hereby declare that the details mentioned above are correct and authentic to the best of my knowledge.

Date: July 4, 2019

Place: Pune Signature

WILSON